https://www.sony.com/en_us/SCA/privacy-policy.html#_CCPA

Last Updated and Effective: May 12, 2020
This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") applies only to the information collected by Sony Corporation of America and Sony’s Card Marketing & Services Company, a division of Sony Electronics Inc., (together, “Sony”), both offline and online, through Sony.com (www.sony.com), the Sony Rewards program (including the Sony Card/PlayStation Card program), the Sony Rewards Website (www.rewards.sony.com), the Sony Rewards mobile application, in connection with the Sony Square NYC experience, and any other websites, and other online or mobile offerings that post a link to this Privacy Policy, whether accessed via computer, mobile device or other technology (collectively, “Properties”).  The websites and properties of affiliated Sony companies, including some that are linked to/from the Properties, may have different privacy policies; therefore, please review the privacy policy notices on those websites or properties if you visit them.
This Privacy Policy explains the information that Sony may collect when you interact with us and our practices with respect to that information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. In addition, please review the applicable Terms and Conditions for the Properties, which governs your use of the Properties.
Collection of Information
Information You Provide to Sony
We may ask you to provide information that could reasonably be used to contact you or to identify you personally (such as first and last name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number, mobile phone number, last 4 digits of social security number (for Sony Card/PlayStation cardholders), photos of both people and objects, and videos) ("Personal Information"). If you choose not to provide this information, you may not be able to access parts of or otherwise participate in the Properties or a particular feature we offer. If you provide us with photos or videos, such images may include metadata which can indicate information about the images, including but not limited to, where and when the image was taken.
We may also ask you to provide other information about yourself, such as demographic information (such as gender, zip code, age, etc.) or payment information or certain information about your preferences and interests. If we combine demographic or other information we collect about you with Personal Information about you, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information.
Sony.com, the Sony Rewards Program and any other Properties are open only to individuals who are 16 years of age and older. We do not knowingly seek or collect information from persons younger than 16 years of age. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected Personal Information from a person younger than 16 years of age through the Properties, we will take reasonable measures to delete such information from our records.
Information Sony Collects Automatically
In addition to any information, including Personal Information, that you choose to submit to the Properties, whenever you visit or interact with the Properties, Sony, as well as any third-party analytics providers or other service providers, may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how the Properties are accessed and used ("Usage Information"). Usage Information may include, without limitation, browser type, operating system, the page served, time on the Properties, and the preceding page views. Usage Information is treated as Personal Information where required by law.
Sony may also automatically collect your IP address or other unique identifiers ("Device Identifiers") for the computer, mobile device, technology or other device (collectively, "Devices") you use to access the Properties. A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device when you access a property or its servers, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier. Some mobile service providers may also provide us or our third-party service providers with information regarding the physical location of the Device used to access the Properties.
The technologies used on the Properties to collect Usage Information, including Device Identifiers, include:
Cookies.  "Cookies" (which may be html files, Flash files or other technology) are small text files that help store user preferences and activity.  A Cookie is placed on a Device when that Device is used to access or visit the Properties. Cookies may be used for many purposes, such as remembering you and your preferences, tracking your visits to our Properties and customizing your experience on the Properties. You may configure your browser or Device to block the use of certain cookies. However, please note that if you choose to disable cookies on your Device, some features of our Properties and our online offerings may not function properly.
Web Beacons.  “Web beacons” (also known as image tags, pixel tags, clear GIFS or web bugs) are small pieces of code used to collect advertising data, such as counting page views, promotion views or advertising responses. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for various purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Properties, to monitor how users navigate the Properties, to count how many sent e-mails were actually opened or to determine whether content sent was actually viewed.
Embedded Scripts. An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Properties, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Properties, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.
Please note that third parties may collect Personal Information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you visit or use the Properties or other online websites and services. For example, some third parties' embedded content or plugins on the Properties, such as social media sharing tools, allow their operators to learn that you have visited or interacted with our Properties, and they may combine this information with other, identifiable information they have collected about your visits to other websites or online services. These third parties may handle this information, and other information they directly collect through their content and plugins, pursuant to their own privacy policies.
Online Tracking. Some web browsers incorporate a “Do Not Track” feature that signals to websites that you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked.  How browsers communicate the Do Not Track signal is not yet uniform. For this reason, our Properties do not respond to such signals, except where required by law.
Ad Serving and Traffic Measurement Services We May Use
Sony licenses technology to serve advertisements on its Properties and within its videos and other content as that content is served across the Internet. In addition, Sony may use third party network advertisers to serve advertisements on the Properties and third-party analytics service providers to evaluate and provide us with information about the use of the Properties and viewing of our content. We do not share the information that you provide to Sony, such as your name and/or email address with these third parties, but ad network providers, the advertisers, the sponsors, and/or analytics service providers may set and access their own cookies, web beacons and embedded scripts on your Device from our Properties. These cookies, web beacons, and embedded scripts may collect Personal Information or other information about your use of the Properties over time and other third-party websites or applications and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, including Usage Information. Cookies and web beacons, including those set by third party network advertisers, may be used to, among other things, target advertisements, prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times, or conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you.
To opt-out of such Cookies, please exercise choice below:
To generally opt-out of interest-based advertising on mobile-optimized or desktop websites, please visit the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) or the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI). For our mobile application, please update your device settings. Please note that by opting out of such Cookies, you may still receive advertisements, but the network from which you opted out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your interests.
In order to opt-out of Google Analytics, which is used to understand how visitors interact with our Properties, please visit: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Please review your Internet browser settings, typically under the sections "Help" or "Internet Options," to exercise choices you have for certain Cookies that are not part of the DAA or NAI.
For instructions on how to configure your browser settings to reject Cookies being served by companies that are not part of the DAA or NAI, click here or go to  https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/. You can also delete all cookies that are already on your computer's hard drive by searching for and deleting files with "cookie" in it.
Additional Opt-Out Choices: You may configure your browser or Device to block the use of certain Cookies.
Please note that without certain Cookies, it may make it difficult for you to use certain features on the Properties.
Information We Receive from Third Parties
Sony may receive information about you from third parties, including service providers working on Sony’s behalf. For example, if you choose to apply for a Sony or PlayStation branded credit card or if you are a Sony or PlayStation branded credit card holder, we may receive information about you from the issuing bank (currently, Comenity Bank), which may include Personal Information as well as information regarding how you use the Sony or PlayStation branded credit card. In addition, if you are on another property and you opt-in to receive information from us, that property may forward to us your e-mail address and other information about you so that we may contact you as requested. We may also supplement the information we collect about you with outside records from third parties to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We may combine the information we receive from these third parties with information we collect. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to any Personal Information received, unless we have disclosed otherwise.
Social Media Applications
Functionality on the Properties may permit interactions between the Properties and third-party properties, such as Facebook and Twitter. Such functionality enables you to “like” a product or online content, “share” content to other properties, and otherwise link the Properties with another third-party property. If you choose to “like” or “share” content or to otherwise post information from or via the Properties to a third-party property, that information may become public and the third-party property may have access to information about you and your use of the Properties.
You may also choose to participate in a third-party application or feature (such as Facebook applications or a similar application or feature on a third-party property, or otherwise linking the Properties with another property) through which you allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about you, including Personal Information. When you choose to participate, you may be opting to link your activity on our Properties with that third-party property, which may then collect information about your visits to our Properties and may publish that activity as you request to your "profile" or similar feature with that third party (such as if you choose to share content you find on one of our Properties with your "connections" on the third party's property). The information we collect is subject to this Privacy Policy. However, the information collected and stored by the third party remains subject to the third party's privacy practices, including whether the third party continues to share information with us or with other third parties, the types of information shared, and your choices regarding what is visible to others on that third party's property. The third party may allow you to remove an application or feature, in which case we will no longer collect information about you through the application or feature, but we may retain the information previously collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Third Party Content, Links to Other Properties and Services, and Sony Content on Other Websites
Certain content on the Properties may be hosted and served by third parties, which may include third party widgets (such as those that allow you to "like" or "share" content with third party websites and interactive services or to provide ratings and reviews). In addition, when you are on the Properties you may be directed to other websites that are operated and controlled by third parties that are beyond our control. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use our logo(s) as part of a co-branding agreement. In addition, Sony content and widgets may be included on web pages and websites that are not associated with us and over which we have no control. These other websites may send their own cookies to your Device, and they may independently collect data or solicit Personal Information. Sony is not responsible for the privacy practices of any third party.
How Sony Uses the Information It Collects and Your Choices
Sony will use the information it collects, including your Personal information: (i) to create your Sony account that can be used to sign-in to various Sony group services; (ii) to process and allow your registration and participation in the Sony Rewards Program, and other features and products we and Sony affiliates offer, including, at times, to verify that the e-mail address you provide is active and valid; (iii) to provide you with requested content, including newsletters; (iv) to tailor the content, advertisements, and offers you see and to determine which products we offer might interest you; (v) to provide you with information about your account and products, services, promotions, or offerings that may be of interest to you; (vi) to improve the Properties and our products and services; (vii) for internal business purposes; (viii) to contact you with regard to your use of the Properties, your account, and, in our discretion, changes to any of our policies; (ix) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your Personal Information; and (x) otherwise with your consent. If you have both a Sony account and a Sony Card account (or a PlayStation Card account), you may link the accounts together. To change or update the Personal Information you have provided to Sony, you may be able to update your account yourself by using your account settings. For example, if you are a Sony Rewards account holder, please visit the “My Account” tab of the Sony Rewards Website for the information you wish to revise or update.
You may be able to indicate your contact preferences at the time you register to create a Sony account or join the Sony Rewards Program. If you are a Sony Rewards account holder, you may also update your preferences by visiting the “Preferences” section of the “My Account” section of the Sony Rewards Website. In all instances, you may opt out of receiving marketing emails by following the opt-out instructions provided to you in those e-mails. If you sign up to receive SMS or MMS messages that may be offered by Sony, you may unsubscribe from any SMS or MMS messages received by replying "STOP”.  Please note that even if you opt out and/or unsubscribe, we reserve the right to send you certain transactional communications relating to your account or use of the Properties. In accordance with our routine record keeping, we may delete certain records that contain Personal Information you have submitted through the Properties or otherwise. We are under no obligation to store such Personal Information indefinitely.
When and With Whom Sony May Share Information Collected
California residents, please see the section below regarding your California privacy rights.
We may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregate user statistics, demographic information, and Usage Information with third parties for a variety of purposes, including tailoring Sony promotions, advertising and communications we present to you.
We may also share your information, including your Personal Information, as disclosed at the time you provide your information, as set forth in this Privacy Policy and in the following circumstances:
Sony. We may share your Personal Information within and among entities affiliated with or related to us that are in the Sony group of companies (collectively, “Affiliates”), some of which are outside the scope of this Privacy Policy, for any purpose, including but not limited to, (i) providing you with or contacting you about content, products, services or other offerings, such as games, videos, music, and software; (ii) business development; (iii) community administration or development; (iv) support of various business processes; (v) security; (vi) research and development; and (vii) enable us to link your accounts and Usage Information between and amongst certain Sony properties. We may also share your Personal Information as indicated above so that Affiliates may use your information in connection with any of the purposes described above in the Section entitled “How Sony Uses the Information It Collects.” Affiliates that do not use this Privacy Policy will handle your information in accordance with their own privacy policies, the terms of which may be different than this Privacy Policy.
Third Parties Providing Services on Our Behalf. We may from time to time employ third parties to perform functions on our behalf; examples include hosting or operating the Properties; sending e-mail, mobile message communications, and other communications; providing customer support; executing interactive voice response (IVR) programs; and performing data analysis. We may share Personal Information with third parties for them to provide content, complete a requested transaction or otherwise perform services for Sony. We and our Affiliates may also share your Personal Information with third-party advertising partners and with co-promotion partners.
When You Consent to Have Your Personal Information Shared or Otherwise Request That We Share Your Information. We or our Affiliates may offer you the opportunity to receive information and/or marketing offers from third parties or to otherwise consent to the sharing of your information with a third party. If you choose to have your Personal Information shared, your Personal Information will be disclosed to the third party and the Personal Information you disclose will be subject to the privacy policy and business practices of that third party. If you consent to receiving communications from third parties, you will need to communicate with them directly if you later decide that you no longer wish to receive their communications. You also may request, sometimes through your use of an interactive feature or third-party application, that we share information about you with a third party and we will typically do so under those circumstances.
Business Transfers.  Sony or any of its assets, including the Properties and the Sony account,  and Sony Rewards Program may be sold, or other transactions may occur in which your Personal Information is one of the key business assets for the transaction. In such a case, your Personal Information may be one of the business assets we transfer. Hence, Sony and our Affiliates reserve the right to disclose and transfer user information, including Personal Information in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, reorganization, the sale of certain stock and/or assets, or other corporate change including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process.
Legal Protections and Law Enforcement. We may transfer and disclose information, including your Personal Information, Usage Information and Device Identifiers (including IP addresses), to third parties: to comply with a legal obligation; to prevent fraud; when we believe in good faith that the law requires it; at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; to verify or enforce Sony’s Terms and Conditions or other applicable policies; to respond to an emergency; or otherwise to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, visitors to our Properties or the public. We may also use Device Identifiers to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, Internet service providers, wireless service providers or law enforcement agencies, in our discretion. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.
Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions. We, our Affiliates, and our third-party partners may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (each, a “Promotion”) that may require registration. If you choose to enter a Promotion, your Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with the administration of such Promotion, such as in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law, such as on a winners list. By entering a Promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor and/or other parties to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing materials.
Co-Promotion Partners:  The Properties may offer opportunities to enter a contest or sweepstakes or other feature that we offer jointly with a third party.  As a result of your participation in such feature, your information may be shared by us or our Affiliates with the third party that is jointly offering the feature, which will be disclosed at the time your information is collected.
Information You Disclose Publicly on Our Properties
Our Properties may offer the opportunity to submit photographs, writings, music, video, audio recordings, computer graphics, pictures, data, questions, comments, suggestions or other content, including Personal Information (collectively, "User Submissions"). To participate, you may be asked to select a username, screen name, member name and/or password. Please do not use your real name or the real name of another person when selecting a username (or screen name or member name).
Note that User Submissions that you post are public. Information you choose to post may be viewed, collected, used or shared with third parties by others. If you choose to voluntarily disclose User Submissions, the protections of this Privacy Policy will not cover such disclosure of information. Think carefully before you post and use caution before disclosing any Personal Information.
User Submissions may be published online or offline in any media or format (currently existing or hereafter developed). We may also publish your name, voice, likeness and other Personal Information with your User Submissions, and Sony may use the content, or any portion of the content, for advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities.
Security; Retention and Monitoring
Unless otherwise required by law, we are not responsible for monitoring or recording any activity on the Properties, including communications, although we reserve the right to do so.
To help protect you and others, we monitor use of the Properties, and we use the Personal Information and other information we collect, in order to:  identify fraudulent activities and transactions; prevent abuse of and investigate and/or seek prosecution for any potential threats to or misuse of the Properties; ensure compliance with the applicable terms of service and this Privacy Policy; investigate violations of or enforce these agreements; and otherwise to protect the rights and property of us, our partners, and customers.  Monitoring may result in the collection, recording, and analysis of online activity or communications through the Properties.  If you do not consent to these conditions, you must discontinue your use of the Properties.
We seek to maintain reasonable security measures designed to help protect your information against unauthorized or accidental disclosure, access, misuse, loss, or alteration. There is no such thing as perfect security. Although we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.
We may retain information about you as long as it is necessary for us to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy.  In addition, we may retain your information for an additional period as is permitted or required to, among other things, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce agreements.  Where and when required by applicable law, we shall delete your information.  Even if we delete your information from active databases, the information may remain on backup or storage media.
Consent to Processing
The Properties are operated in and intended for use in the United States. If you are located in the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using the Properties, or providing us with any information, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen.
California Privacy Notice
Our Practices Regarding Collection and Use of your CA Personal Information
If you reside in California, we are required to provide additional information to you about how we collect, use and disclose your information, and you may have additional rights with regard to how we use your information. We have included this California-specific information below.
CA Personal Information. Consistent with the "Collection of Information" section above, we may collect certain categories of information about California residents ("CA Personal Information"), specifically:
Personal Identifiers: such as, first and last name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, age, last 4 digits of social security number, username and password for our Properties;
Other Identifiers: such as, Device Identifiers, IP address, or other unique identifiers;
Commercial Information: such as, points earned and redemption histories, products or services purchased, obtained or considered, other purchasing, payment information, transaction history;
Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity: Such as Usage Information, computer and connection information, browser type, operating system, page views, traffic to and from the websites, advertising data and other standard weblog information collected via cookies, web beacons, and related tracking technologies;
Geolocation Data: physical location information through the use of our Properties on your mobile phone or Device by, for example using satellite, cell phone tower, WiFi signal, beacons, Bluetooth and near field communication protocols;
Audio, Visual and Similar Electronic Information: such as pictures you may send to us; and
Other Consumer Characteristics: such as user profile or inferences drawn from purchase or browsing history.
Sources of CA Personal Information. Consistent with the "Collection of Information" section above, we may collect CA Personal Information from the following sources:
Directly from Consumers: such as when you voluntarily provide CA Personal Information to us or our service providers when purchasing products or services or registering on our Properties;
Third-Party Business Partners: such as retail stores or website marketing partners;
Third-Party Applications: such as social networks;
Advertising Networks: such as ad technology partners that collect information via cookies, web beacons, and related tracking technologies; and
Data Resellers: such as market research firms and data aggregators we have relationships with.
Use of CA Personal Information. Consistent with the "How Sony Uses the Information It Collects and Your Choices" section above, we may use CA Personal Information for the following business or commercial purposes:
CA Personal Information Sold or Disclosed For Business Purposes. In the preceding twelve months, we may have shared the following categories of CA Personal Information for business purposes: Identifiers, Commercial Information, Internet or Other Electronic Activity, Geolocation Data.
California Consumer Rights. Subject to certain exceptions, as a California resident, you may have the following rights to your CA Personal Information:
Access. Request access to your CA Personal Information that we have collected, used, disclosed, or sold within the preceding 12 months;
Deletion. Request deletion of your CA Personal Information; and
CA Personal Information Sold or Disclosed For Business Purposes. Request information about the CA Personal Information we have "sold" (as defined under CCPA) or disclosed for business purposes within the preceding 12 months.
Please note, if you request deletion of your CA Personal Information, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we may be required to retain some of your CA Personal Information to fulfill consumer requests. In addition, certain CA Personal Information is strictly necessary in order for us to fulfill the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. If you wish to exercise a right listed in this section, you may submit a request to the relevant Property using the following links:
Access Request for Sony.com
Access Request for Sony Rewards
Deletion Request for Sony.com
Deletion Request for Sony Rewards
Exercising Your Rights. If you are a California resident and wish to exercise any of these rights, please: (a) access the webform applicable to your request as described above; or (b) call the following toll-free number, 1-800-314-1552, if your request is regarding Sony.com, or 1-800-299-3485, if your request is regarding Sony Rewards. When submitting your request, you must include your first and last name, and email address. We are not responsible for requests that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information. You may be asked to provide additional proof of identification so that we can verify your identity, and we may require that you validate the request. Please note that you are limited by law in the number of requests you may submit per year.
We will not discriminate against you by offering you different pricing or products, or by providing you with a different level or quality of products, or in connection with Promotions and other offerings, based solely upon you exercising your rights to your CA Personal Information.
Authorized Agents: To the extent that you elect to designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf, they must provide appropriate documentation including a written signed permission form from you, proof of your identity, and verification of their identity; or a valid, designated power of attorney, as required under the California Probate Code. We may require additional proof of authority or may need to contact you directly to validate the request.
“Do Not Sell My Personal Information.” You have the right to opt-out of the sale of your CA Personal Information. If you wish to exercise this right,  you may submit a request to Sony Rewards here or call the following toll-free number, 1-800-299-3485. Please note that Sony.com does not sell your personal information.
Policy Governs Use: Changes to Privacy Policy
Sony reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice to you, and any changes will become effective immediately upon posting, so please review this Privacy Policy periodically. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on the Properties prior to the change becoming effective.
Questions
If you have any questions or comments about our practices regarding Personal Information or about this Privacy Policy, please write to us at Sony, 25 Madison Avenue, New York, New York 10010, Attn: Legal Department, or submit your request via email at privacy@sonyusa.com.
Click here to access PDF version for printing
Where To BuySee Authorized RetailersSony RewardsJoin NowLearn MoreManage AccountNews & InfoPress ReleasesAbout SonyProduct SupportProduct ManualsElectronics RegistrationElectronics NewsletterAccessibilityOther SitesProfessional Products & SolutionsPlayStationSony PicturesSony MusicSony MobileB2B Premium IncentiveUnited StatesCareersContact UsCompany InfoVoluntary RecallLike us on FacebookVisit us on FacebookFollow us on TwitterVisit us on TwitterFollow us on InstagramView on InstagramFollow us on TumblrVisit us on TumblrFacebookTwitterInstagramTumblr
